



# **Professional Summary**

Over 7 years of experience as a software developer in designing and developing Rich User Interface applications, integrating with various Databases and Client-Server applications in iPhone/iPad (IOS 4.0 - IOS 10, Xcode 4.0 - 8.0) application development using Objective C and Swift. Excellent communication, organizational skills, attention to detail and the ability to meet tight deadlines.

# **Work Experience**

## Senior los Developer II

Lowes Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Mooresville, NC

- Worked on Xcode 7, Swift, Obj C, for developing Lowes Applications for Consumer and Associate teams.
- Integrated the Webservices using Alamofire in Swift to GET or POST the request.
- Worked with the Lowes Custom Pods, to maintain the standard across the applications.

## **Senior Ios Developer**

Delta Corporation Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Los Angeles, CA

- · Capital One ShareBuilder is an online brokerage firm.
- Investors can easily buy stocks, bonds, options, mutual funds, and exchange-traded funds as partial shares via Automatic Investing and Portfolio Builder.
- Real-time trading is also available online, on mobile devices, and via telephone.

#### **Education**

#### Master's In Computer Science

University Of Tsukuba - Tsukuba, Japan Jan / 2019 - Ongoing New York

Skills			
IOS	Swift	Objective C	Xcode

### **Achievements**

Award